ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Photographs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Item 6: Photo: Vicki Williams, Publication (Box 13, Folder 42)
    By Joanne Durham. April 15, 1988. Item is in English.
- "A Different, Union Army" - Master, Publication (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: A Different Union Army Invades the South, Publication (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Workers Leaflet - cc's after 1st bargaining, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Last Monday November 20, 1989 A Day to Remember, Publication (Box 13, Folder 44)
    November 27, 1989. Item is in English.
- Lichtenberg: NAACP communications, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Lichto: Boycott Leaflets, Updates, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Unfair Labor Practice Strike Underway at Delila, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Wednesday, October 26, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: This Holiday Season Looks Dark for Lichtenberg Drapery Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
    December (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
- Lichto: FTC Docs, 1984-1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Continuing Guaranty Under the Textile Fiber Products Identification Act, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
    By Alan Lichtenberg. September 8, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Delila MFG. Knit Spear Department Spear Side Hem Rates, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
    October 24, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: "My name is Carolyn Flourney.", Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
    By Anthony Rowan. Monday, November 21, 1994. Item is in English.
- Lichto: Corporate Finance, 1986-1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: S. Lichtenberg v. ACTWU Comparison of Corporate Financial Reposts, 1986-1988 Attorney Work Product, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Bob Giolito. January 10, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1986 Corporation Franchise or Income Tax Return, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    January 20, 1990. Item is in English.
- Lic: Store Sales, 1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: S Lichtenberg: Gross Sales By Major ($ Thousands), Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Friday, March 23, 1990. Item is in English.
- S. Lichtenberg Press Releases, 1988; Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: History Workers at the Samsons and Delila Plants, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: ACTWU to Kick Off National Campaign for Lichtenberg Workers Joseph Lowery to Speak at Waynesboro Rally, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    By Joan Carter. Thursday, March 23, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: ACTWU Wins Elections in Tennessee and Georgia, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    By Nancy Peckenham. Saturday, April 16, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: We're Voting "Yes" For a Better Future, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Campaign for Justice: S. Lichtenberg and Company, Inc., 1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Information Packet S. Lichtenberg & Company, Inc. Samsons and Delila Manufacturing Plants Waynesboro and Louisville, GA, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Joanne Durham/Nancy Peckenham. March 15, 1988 - May 4, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: At S. Lichtenberg & Co. 650 Curtain and Drapery Workers Need Your Help!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: EEOC Discrimination Charges Filed Against The S. Lichtenberg Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Statement By Rep. John Lewis. January 20, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Wake Up for We Too Have a Dream, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Sharon Roberson, Samsons Worker. February 23, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Benjamin L. Hooks and Georgia NAACP State Conference President Call for Support of Textile Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Conyers Asks Labor Department's Contracts Compliance Office to Investigate Charges of Widespread Employment Discrimination by Textile Manufacturer Supplying Products to the Military, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Thursday, March 23, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: OSHA Fines Owner of 2 Factories, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Attention Bath, Bed and Linen Show Participants: OSHA Cites S. Lichtenberg & Co., Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Metro Detroit Supports Struggle of Southern Textile Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    May 18, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Testimony of Sharon A. Roberson to the House Select Committee on Children, Youth and Families "Hearings on Working Families on the Margin: The Uncertain Future of America's Small Towns", Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Resolution of the Detroit City Council, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Rsolution by Council Member Maryann Mahaffey. February 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: It's Crunch Time at Samsons and Delila, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Rev. Wendell Anthony. April 21/26, 1989. Item is in English.
- Connective Ministry Across the South - report to Citizens Commission on Justice at Hanes, 1983; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  March 21, 1983
  - Item 1: Report to the Citizen Commission On Justice At Hanes, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    By Prepared by Sister Imeda Maurer. March 21, 1983. Item is in English.
- Lichto: Press Packets, 1988-1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Textile Companies Sue Union for $68 Million, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Cas Shearin. Saturday, June 10, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: S. Lichtenberg and Co. Charged with 61 Counts of Discharge for Union Activity, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Nancy Peckenham. Monday, June 19, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Backgrounder on S. Lichtenberg & Co., Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Chronology of Legal Actions Throughout S. Lichtenberg Employees' Organizing Drive, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    January 19 - April 22, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Textile Workers Call for Contract From S. Lichtenberg & Co., Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Jo-Ann Mort/Matthew Walker. Thursday May 5th (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: We Took Our Struggle to N.Y., Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Nickey Thomas. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: We Go To Customers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Shop Stewards Samsons & Delila. November 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: News Letter Board Adopts Convention Travel Fund, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Fanfare Salutes Keyville's Struggle And King's Dream, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Wake Up For We Too Have A Dream, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Sharon Roberson, Samsons Worker. January 14, 1989. Item is in English.
- Clippings (June-Oct.) and NAACP Resolution, 1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Workers Visit Capital to Lobby Congressmen in Labor Dispute, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Lichtenberg, 1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: ACTWU Gets NLRB Decision, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Spinning Yarns & Shirt Tales, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By Saunders. July - August 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Dear Fellow Samsons and Delila, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    May 23, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: I Was A Victim, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By Mary Rucker. May 10, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: 1989 The Year in Review, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    December 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Company Pets Slide By With Anything!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    October 13, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Lichtenbergs Supervisors Are Unjust, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: The Lichtenbergs Strike Again Mary Bell Unjustly Fired After 11 1/2 Years, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By Harold Galloway. October 13, 1989/May 25 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Conversation w/Fred Daniel / Montgomery Ward, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    April 26 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Haven't You Had Enough?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    March 3, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Victory on the Christmas Club, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    February 23, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: It's Another Union Victory, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    February 26, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: EEOC Discrimination Suit Filed, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: ACTWU At The Market Show, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    May 9, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: It's Official, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    October 17, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: It's Union Time at Samsons and Delila!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    November 2, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Lichtenberg's - Let's Bargain!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    October 26, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Union Meeting, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Tuesday, November 28, Wednesday, November 29, Saturday, December 2, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Company Wants To Piecemeal Bargain, Again!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    August 8, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: ACTWU Doesn't Need Another Election!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    June 21, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Dear Fellow Samsons and Delila Employees, STOP AND LISTEN., Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By Shop Stewards and Pro Union Leaders of Samsons and Delila. June 13, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Lichtenberg Workers Honor Dr. M.L.King Keep Dream Alive!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Lichto: Other Union and UFCW Assistance, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Action at Family Dollar, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Major Customer Boycotting Lichtenberg, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Lichto - CEO letters faxed 11/21, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Fax Transmission Sheet, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    By Hillary Horn. November 28, 1994. Item is in English.
- Lichto/JCP 1994, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: *Lichtenberg Boycott Newsflash* J.C. Penney Can't Play Dumb!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Licht: Letter to Customers #1, 10/26/94, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Licht: "On-Strike" Leaflet 1994, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Lichtenberg on Strike!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Licht: Customer Letter#2, 11/10/94, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Licht: Moseley-Braun Ltr., 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Photo - workers at Licht. HQ, 1988; Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Lichtenberg & Co. at Corporate Offices in New York, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
    By Photo: Jim Obst. May 5, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Demostration at Lichtenberg Co. Manhattan Headquarters, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
    By Jim Obst. May 5, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Corporate Action at S. Lichtenberg Office, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Lichto: Clips, 1990, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Day That "Jesse" Came to Town, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
    By Pearl Stamper. Thursday, January 18, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Services Nationwide Honor King, Assess 'Dream', Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
    By Associated Press. Monday, January 15, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Unionist Celebrate Dr. King, Push for Nationwide Holiday, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Firm Accused of Discrimination, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
    By Juanita Bratcher. Wednesday, February 7, 1990. Item is in English.
- Lichto: Networks Activated, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Notes Re S. Lichtenberg Campaign, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: A New Issues-Oriented JLC Publication, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Plain Paper Labels, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: All Names Below Wrote Separate Letterhead Letters:, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
    By Pheobe McKinney. November 12, 1990. Item is in English.
- JLC Letters, 1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Atlanta Const. - City Comm. 5/16/89, 1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Group Backs Workers in Labor Dispute, Publication (Box 14, Folder 23)
    By Shelia M. Poole. Tuesday, May 16, 1989. Item is in English.
- Lichtenberg: Settlement, 1991-1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Textile Union Approves Contract, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
    By Mike Wynn. Thursday, October 17, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Lichtenberg Workers OK Contract, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Thursday, October 17, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Workers, Union Archieve Historic Settlement At S. Lichtenberg; Meeting Set On Ratification Of First Contract, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
    By Kim Klesty. Wednesday, October 16, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Jesse Jackson to Rally Workers in East Georgia, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
    By Shelia M. Poole. Tuesday, May 1, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Lichtenberg Told to Rehire Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Barbara Hines Lewis - poem, Publication (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Only The Strong Can Survive, Publication (Box 14, Folder 25)
    By Barbara Hines Lewis, Delila Plant. Unknown Date/Publication. Item is in English.
- Workers' Leaflets, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Company Violated Court Order, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
    By Joanne. February 5, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What About The Raise!!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
    January 25, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Petition for Wage Increase, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
    By Shop Stewards. January 24, 1990. Item is in English.
- Orig. - Worker Newsletter Mailing, 12/20/89, 1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Wakees' Newsletter, Publication (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Solidarity, 1989, Publication (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Solidarity, Publication (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Discrimination. - Cases and Statutes, 1988; Publication (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Lay Off w/8 Discrim! And Race or Racial, Publication (Box 14, Folder 29)
    July 20, 1988. Item is in English.
- Lichtenberg: Village Voice Article, 1991; Publication (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Giants in the Land of Cotton, Publication (Box 14, Folder 30)
    By Jonathan Tasani. October 22, 1991. Item is in English.
- Wal-Mart, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Lichtenberg Campaign Review, 1991, Publication (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Struggle For Justice At Samsons and Delila: A Chronology, Publication (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: The Lichtenberg Campaign: Chronology of Significant Legal Events, Publication (Box 14, Folder 32)
    January 19, 1988 - July 6, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Highlights Of The Settlement, Publication (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Lic: December '89-April '90, Key Store Correspondent, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Burlington, 1991; Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Court Finds No Brisa Violation by Company That Broke Pledge to Contribute Plan Surplus, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
    By Jack Sheinkman. October 6, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees Left Holding the Bag, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: The Magician's Last Trick, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
    By Terence P. Pare. May 20, 1991. Item is in English.